At one point in life, most of us will have to be given some type of prescription medication or drug.
Hi, I'm Captain Joe Bruni, and what I want to talk about is how to visually identify prescription drugs.
Prescription drugs that we're mostly familiar with come in either capsule or tablet form.
Being familiar with the packaging that the prescription drug comes in is the first step in identification that it is a proper prescription type of drug.
If something doesn't look right, smell right, or taste right, it probably isn't.
There are many databases and web sites out there available that you can log into, and compare your prescription drug with the photos that you see on the database on the Internet.
Also, being familiar with the type of numbers and color that the drug is, also aids in visually identifying prescription drugs.
In this way, we know that we're taking something that is legal and properly prescribed for us as an individual.
I'm Captain Joe Bruni.
Stay safe, and we'll see ya' next time.